business trips
[Music]
so let's practice these safety
precautions and promise ourselves a
safer healthier future
together we can win the fight against
covet 19.
[Music]
cookie
restart right
[Music]
you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
right
[Music]
hey
foreign
[Music]
looks like
good afternoon ladies
on behalf of the company and my
colleagues on the board of directors
welcome you all to the 21st annual
general meeting agm of the company
i hope you are all
keeping safe and well
the impact of the second wave was more
widespread
even among those who did not get
infected by the virus many witness their
family members or close associates
getting affected
i would like to stress
on the point that collectively it is
everybody's responsibility to get
vaccinated and continue exercise portion
and follow social distancing norms and
guidelines issued by the government
in view of the ongoing covet 19 pandemic
consequent restrictions and your safety
in mind
we are holding the agm through video
conference in dc
other audio visual means oavm
in accordance with the circulars issued
by the ministry of corporate affairs in
snail and the securities and exchange
board of india city
we have the requisite quorum present
through video conference to conduct the
proceedings of the meetings
participation of members from video
conference is being written for the
purpose of quorum
as per the circulars issued by mca and
section 103 of the company is act 2013
the forum being present i call this
meeting to order
before we start the main proceedings of
the meeting i request my colleagues
joining this meeting through vc to
introduce themselves one by one to the
shareholders of the company mentioning
name designation and place
first let me begin with myself
chairman of the chairperson of the
company i am attending this meeting from
icsa lombard office in mumbai
mr bhargava dasgupta agra front and
bargain
a managing director and ceo attending
this meeting from our office in isis
in mumbai thank you
ashwin
good afternoon i am ashwin parikh
attending this agent from my residence
in mumbai
i am an independent director and
chairman of the audit committee thank
you
mr udair
good afternoon i am
attending this annual general meeting
from my residence in mumbai
i am an independent director and
chairman of the board nomination and
remuneration committee thank you
mr suresh
good afternoon i am suresh kumar
attending this meeting from my residence
in dubai i am an independent director
and chairman of the stakeholders
relationship committee thank you
good afternoon
i
am independent director attending this
agm from my residence in gunawala thank
you
good afternoon i am
independent director
attending this agent from a residence in
mumbai thank you
mrs
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
director attending this agm from icsa
lombard office in mumbai thank you
mr sanjeev
good afternoon
executive director attending this agency
apart from the board of directors we
also have mr gopal chandra chief
financial officer and chief risk officer
and mr vikas mehra company secretary of
the art company attending this meeting
from this room the senior management of
the company are joining the agent from
their respective locations
accountants
and mr r surya narayanan partner
llp chartered accountants the joint
statutory auditors of the company have
joined this agm from their respective
locations
mr vivi tolaviya designated partner of
the lake and associates llp secretary in
auditor the company has joined the agm
from his respective location
practicing company secretaries
scrutinizer of the agent has also joined
this agent
from her respective location
i sincerely thank all the shareholders
of the company who have joined this
meeting from vc the company has made
necessary arrangements to ensure
participation of members at this meeting
through video conference and to enable
them to vote on the resolution set forth
in the notice electronically
trust all of you have referred the
general instructions for e-voting and
participation in the meeting
in case members face any difficulty they
may reach out on the helpline numbers
given on page number 12 of the notice of
the agm under the head instructions for
members attending the agm through vc
stroke olva
as the agm is being held through vc
facility for appointment of proxies by
the members was not applicable and hence
the company has not provided proxy forms
to its members and did not maintain
proximate proxy register the statutory
registers other relevant documents and
the annual certificate on implementation
of employee stock options team from
statutory auditors of the company are
made available electronically for
inspection by the members during this
agm and nsdl e-voting system
not just convening the meeting
coming to the business of the meeting
with your permission i shall now take
the notice convening this meeting as
ready
report of the auditors in line with the
provisions of the companies act 2013
only the qualifications observations or
adverse remarks of the auditors on
financial transactions or matters are
required to be read after the meeting of
the shareholders
the joint statutory auditor's report on
the financial statements and the
secretarial audit report for the
financial year ending march 31st 2021 do
not contain any qualifications
observations or adverse remarks
accordingly the state reports are not
required to be read at this meeting
for the benefit of the shareholders we
have arranged for an audio visual
presentation which would be screened
two glorious decades of pursuing one
unified mission
the mission to deliver on the promises
rcic lombard our relentless pursuit of
standing by our brand ethos of nepali
body has completed an illustrious
journey of 20 years
[Music]
in these 20 years together with our
power team
supportive stakeholders and loyal
customers
we have carved a leadership position for
ourselves in the insurance industry
our early adoption of modern technology
in creating user-friendly digital
journeys has given us a lead in
delivering innovative tech enabled
solutions to our customers
that is why in the face of the
unprecedented challenges of the pandemic
we have been able to ensure complete
service continuity to our customers and
making sure that we are able to meet
their insurance related needs in a safe
contactless manner
our oil take care app is a step in this
direction
imagine a single stop mobile solution to
address your insurance and wellness
related needs
from tele consultations with doctors to
guidance on nutrition and fitness to
lifestyle based counseling
a revolutionary instaspect facility on
the il take care app empowers customers
to get their vehicle damage assessment
done in real time start by themselves
the benefit instant claim settlement at
any time and from anywhere
in a world where communication has gone
instant we are aligning our
communication to the instant messaging
modes
a cognitive bot enabled whatsapp
platform provides multiple services an
instant query resolution of customers in
a user-friendly way
and when we deploy technology we ensure
that it understands you and speaks to
you in your language
this is all thanks to the ai
capabilities and use of natural language
processing that we have been championing
over the years
customer needs vary from one to the
other for our sme segment we have made
things seamless with our digital sme
website that makes policy purchase
renewal claims etc a seamless and
hassle-free experience
over the years we have enhanced our role
from being a risk financer to becoming a
risk management partner for our
customers
as a result our customers can benefit
from a host of value-added solutions
for instance we offer our corporate
clients hijack solutions for transit
cargo
iot based fire hydrant systems wellness
programs for employees etc
our promise to deliver extends to our
other stakeholders including our channel
partners
we have been supporting them and
leveraging our technology solutions to
service their customers
webinars were organized for over 7 000
channel partners to familiarize them
with our digital tools amid the pandemic
this is not limited to one but all our
business solutions including our partner
myra auto ninja
behind our trust to fulfilling our
promises are our employees to ensure
their safety and well-being we have been
taking many initiatives for them and
their families
we have introduced multiple platforms to
support employees and to keep them
engaged and motivated
hybrid working policy offered the
employees the flexibility of choosing to
either work from home or opt for remote
working or work from office as per their
convenience
to ensure that our employees and channel
partners stay protected against covert
19 protection exclusive vaccination
drives were organized for them
even as we scale high on the business
and customer focused metrics we have
diligently worked on meeting a
sustainability commitment
our various environmental initiatives
continue to make great strides in
minimizing our carbon footprint
energy saving was achieved by installing
led fittings at our corporate offices
as a responsible corporate we continued
to fulfill our promise of going beyond
business and serving the nation in
dealing with the challenges of the
widespread pandemic
[Music]
we have conducted vaccination camps for
senior citizens underprivileged sections
in the last few months
benefiting over 50 000 individuals
in a record initiative we partnered with
the neoshare group to set up a 58 bed
covered care center in just 12 days in
newtown west bengal
our csr efforts also moved a notch
higher this year
taking forward a flagship initiative
ride to safety
we organized over 250 virtual workshops
which benefited over 40 000 families
we distributed over 35 000 specially
designed rsi marked helmets along with
safety masks
[Music]
we also identified the critical needs of
our front line warriors during the
pandemic
we extended a helping hand by
distributing raincoats and masks for
their enhanced safety
a unique employee volunteering
initiative caring hands has grown
exponentially
nine thousand children benefited from
the initiative conducted through a
hybrid method
[Music]
under our niranjani initiative we
organized virtual sessions across 250
schools from mumbai and delhi water
purifiers and sanitizer dispensers were
installed in these schools
as we look ahead we are enthusiastic
about a business growth trajectory
our revenue for fy21 stood at rupees
114.03
billion continuing on the long-term
trajectory
during the first year we shield over 21
million policies and settled more than
1.6 million claims
our profit after tax rose to rupees
14.73 billion
with a
21.7 return on average equity
this was driven by our focus on core
profitability depicted by combined ratio
which stood at
99.8 percent
as we progress
we will stay focused on creating a
long-term sustainable business model and
make way for exponential growth
financial results gain
from all over
we've received several awards for our
all-round performance
in every journey comes some significant
milestones that define the way forward
the proposed merger of party axa general
insurance with icic and lombard will add
philip to our growth story
this integration will make us the second
largest insurer
it will add to an existing set of
customer friendly solutions while
strengthening our business franchisee
as we celebrate this milestone year in
our illustrious journey
we reaffirm our commitment to deliver
honor promises
we stay focused on leading the change
and are committed to create a future
that is positive and reassuring for our
customers
icici lombard nepal body
[Music]
i would like to inform you that pursuant
to the company is act 2001 fee
led with relevant rules and semi listing
regulations the company had provided an
opportunity to all its members to
exercise their voting rights through
electronic voting remote e-voting
for the following items of business to
be transacted at the agent during the
period saturday over 7th to 20 21 9 am
to august 9 20 21 5 pm
members who have not cast their vote
earlier and participating in this
meeting can now cast their votes through
e-voting module made available by nsda
now i propose to take up the business of
the meeting seriation in accordance with
the agm notice
one
to consider to receive consider an
adoptive and audited financial report
statements
for the financial year ended march 31
2021 together with the reports of the
board of directors and auditors there on
two
to confirm payment of interim dividend
on equity shares of the company for the
financial year ended march 31st 2021
3 to declare final dividend on equity
shares of the company but the financial
year ended march 31st 2021
4.
to appoint a director in place of
mr vishakha modi
00203578
who retires by rotation and being
eligible offers herself for
reappointment
5.
to reappoint ms
pkf sridhar and santanam llp chartered
accountants
one of the joint statutory auditors of
the company
6.
to fix the demonstration of message pks
reader and santana llp chartered
accountants and ms
chatham company chartered accountants
join statutory auditors of the company
for fy 2020.
i now request mr uday chittaly to chair
the meeting for agenda item number seven
thank you
agenda item seven pertains to the
reappointment of mrs lalitha
director identification number triple
zero four three five five nine
as a non-executive and non-independent
uh non-executive and independent
director of the company
and this is a matter of a special
business one of the special businesses
[Laughter]
seven seven two eight managing director
of the company
nine
revision and rememberation payable to
aloo kumar agarwad in zero three four
three four
three zero four hold full-time director
designated as executive director
wholesale of the company
division and regulation payable to mr
sanjeev
071-92264 full-time director designated
as executive director retail of the
company
resolutions proposed as item numbers 1
to 6 and 8 to 10 are ordinary
resolutions to be passed with the simple
majority and resolution proposed as item
number seven is a special resolution
the board has appointed mrs ashwini
partner of failing her mr atul mehta
partner of methamphetamine company
secretaries as the scrutinizer for
conducting the e-voting process in a
fair and transparent manner and to
scrutinize the votes cast through remote
e-voting and e-voting through the agent
and to submit the consolidated report of
voting and compliance to the provisions
of the companies act
2030 and the cp lodr regulation 2015.
now i would like to invite speaker
shareholders who have done their prior
registration to speak
members may give their suggestions or
seek clarification
only those members who are holding
equity shares of the company as on
cutoff date for e-voting that is august
3 2021
i am entitled to participate and speak
at the agm
subject to prior registration
with due respect to other speakers and
time
i kindly request each speaker to be
brief and restrict their suggestions
stroke comments to three minutes
on matters are set forth in the notice
annual accounts and operations of the
company
for fy 2021
to avoid repetition the answers to all
the questions will be provided at the
end of the q a session
i now request the moderator to please go
ahead with the q a session
thank you ma'am
ladies and gentlemen our chairperson and
management will now take questions
shareholders who are registered to speak
are requested to kindly switch your
camera on unmute your microphone and
speak when your names are announced
kindly restrict your comments and
queries to a maximum of three minutes
our first share we're going to speak
is ms
hello
good afternoon to all of you my side lei
kasha from mumbai
first of all i'm very much thankful to
our company secretary mr vikashi
especially
our tracer and remember
for resenting
very good investor services
and also sending me the agent notice by
email building them in such a difficult
situation
which is full of knowledge tight and
precise in place
now
i am very happy
to see all the good deeds you have done
during this difficult time
i pray to god that he always shall work
his blessing
upon you
i would thank to all personal company
for receiving awards and recognition by
our various during the year 2021
and i am very glad the company is doing
very well in the field of csr activities
i am sure that our company awards list
will get longer and longer the years to
come
now i would like to ask few questions
my first question is
what are the measures taken by the
company for it employs withdrawal
respect to commit 19.
my second question is
what are the focus area for cooperative
social
responsibility undertaken by the company
my third question is how is our company
operating
are we operating from home or are they
are working from the office
my fourth question is
are all our company employees vaccinated
against coffee 19.
so
i would like to say i strongly propose
all the resolutions for students meeting
and by which best wishes always our
company and this possibility thank you
mom
thank you ma'am
our next shareholder speaker
is santosh saraf
[Music]
me
foreign
well
[Music]
we
foreign
healthiness
ladies and gentlemen foreign next
shareholder speaker is mr yusuf rangwala
mr ramwala could you kindly unloot and
speak
respected
[Laughter]
i'm very happy i am speaking from mumbai
i am very happy to our excellent state
department for giving me a link madam
can you see my face madam
hello sir your camera is officer if you
could please
switch your camera on to be able to see
you
[Music]
mr ambala switch your camera
foreign
[Laughter]
good
your connectivity uh we'll come back to
you after we finish a couple of speakers
so we'll try and sort that out in the
meanwhile this rambla we'll come back to
you in the meanwhile we'll go on to
uh um
[Music]
yeah
yes sir we can hear you and we can see
you clearly go ahead sir
expected forum
director
and officials of the icici lombard
i am shortly known as vijay
there are certain concerns
although i have huge respect for the
forums
there are certain concerns which i have
with icsa
i expect the independent director and
the company secretary to work
in a fair and transparent manner
which i noted
there is a difference
between
certain things being asked by me and the
questions raised to the company's
secretaries are not addressed in timely
manner as well as there is there are
always a delay
there are always trying to
not to answer before not to respond to
any of the questions queries
there are queries and concerns regarding
the bharti exam merger the valuation
part the process and our con our
esteemed company secretary has no answer
to it
to my surprise he says you know for
every query which i addressed to him
secondly also i requested
to uh walk through for the qualification
of independent directors i have huge
respect for them but
as for the safety guidelines as per
other guidelines i have serious concern
about qualification of as an independent
director i find
as for the information available to me
and i asked for it nobody arranged a
call
and as for the information arranged
asked for by me
that no call was arranged and as for the
information available on the public
place or on the earth
notice provided i fear i found the
independent director does not fall in
the definition of independent director
itself
there is a huge cap i found they are
related to company either
either coming from icici bank
or either coming from the
auditing partners
so
i expect the independent
company
to be the custodian of shareholder value
shareholders
maximizing shareholder value
but i find
there is
thank
thank you very much miss vijayawad here
uh we now move on to our next
shareholder speaker mr vinod agarwal
mr agarwal could you kindly unboot your
microphone switch your camera on and
speak
[Music]
hello
mr godwall we can hear you
and we can see you now
i
have gone through your annual
or due to covet and how much extra
payments that would have likely to me
have been made in the health insurance
section of our business due to
it the extra payments
which may not have been accounted
earlier while giving out the policies
this is
the additional loss on the
policy that we would have
occurred due to profit 19 and
uh
front
are we being able to how strong will our
firewalls be since there's a lot of uh
remote of working and work from home
culture
and we have seen even the best of the
organization in america been getting
hacked and
the demands being made for ransom how
strong will our firewalls be on our
technology front since we are spending
says 7.29 billion rupees on technology
upfront so this is one thing and um is
that the rest of the things in the
annual report are there i do not want to
read out the annual report i can't read
out certainly you've done the 140
billion of
this thing your
insurance
pack is 14
billion i can read out i don't read out
i don't want to take up much of your
time sir obviously company all the best
and let the company keep on growing and
says one small query which has remained
with me certainly here declared interim
dividend of four and in the final
dividend you are declaring rupees four
so is it eight rupees that you are
declaring total dividend for the year or
is it in only four rupees that interim
dividend has been taken as the final
dividend for the year for four rupees
this is my another small query i could
not have understood it i'm just uh
seeking a clarification on this thank
you sir signing off we know that one
thank you mr agarwal
will now come back to mr yosuf for
anguala we had a little connectivity
problem we've brought them back on mr
ramwala if you can unmute your camera
your microphone switch your camera on
and go ahead and speak
yes
how we are growing sir and my good
wishes for the
only nothing more to it
i thanks our city partner for giving a
link thank you very much and after queen
19 is over
please keep a small get together
[Laughter]
with that we come to the end of this
section of the agm
okay
i believe we have one of our
shareholders who had logged out earlier
who has logged back in
we'll have mr kirti shah
uh as our final speaker mr kittisha you
are on camera
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you very
much with that we come to the end of
this section of the agm thank you dear
shareholders for your observations and
berries to respond to these i shall now
hand the proceedings back to our
chairperson over to you man
now i request mr bhargava
managing director and ceo to respond to
the queries raised by the shareholders
thank you man
and uh thank you all of you for uh
very insightful questions so let me go
one by one
i'll start with uh
miss lekha shah
thank you ma'am for all the kind words
to the secretary department uh i'm sure
that he will be particularly motivated
based on your
feedback
the specific questions that you had were
uh
one the measures that we took for
employees for uh covet
now one of the uh
approaches that we took right at the
beginning of the pandemic last year was
focusing on employee safety
and
the focus was to ensure that we continue
to operate well uh using technology
while allowing people to work from home
through this process
thereafter over the years you know over
the months we've added a lot of benefits
first we launched schemes to uh provide
them a better technical you know
technology support including laptops
just for everyone
better internet bandwidth we even uh
given the fact that people may not have
you know furniture at home which is
suitable for working for lonna along us
we also seem to
let people buy
office furniture
and our employee at an organization cost
thereafter when the second wave happened
we have launched a number of schemes
starting with the vaccination for
employees and their families
we announced open specifically
we announced
a special uh amount of compensation for
people who got affected by covent for
whom there was home care treatment plus
we have a direct team which was
dedicatedly supporting all our employees
through that phase whenever they needed
some support with hospitals or hospital
beds or any other uh basket so there was
a lot of focus on supporting our
employees during the corporate period
and as a company we all we also
announced that we will continue to
remain hybrid through this period
again to facilitate uh you know the
benefit that we talked about to people
we had similarly a lot of customer uh
initiatives for provide
but you know that is also being detailed
in our in our annual report
you asked a question about what are the
focus areas for csr
there are
four areas that we particularly focus on
two of them has been uh for almost 10
years one one of them is the road safety
initiative which you saw in the video
we've been distributing uh
helmets for children in india helmets
for children were not available at all
even if you wanted to go to a shop you
couldn't buy helmets for children so we
saw that gap and we worked with
isi approved helmet manufacturers to
provide helmets and it's part of our csi
initiative we also go to schools train
people on the importance of road safety
uh you know do workshops with their
parents when we hand over these elements
the second thing that we've been doing
again for a long time almost 10 years
now is an employee volunteering
initiative which we call caring hands
which is where on one day almost all of
us go out to municipal schools and do uh
your eye camps for students of these
schools typically from class 6 to class
8 and based on what we see we then
provide
rectification you know solutions support
me in terms of
just some advice or even in terms of
providing spectacles to these students
who may not even realize that they have
a you know problem with power and in
some cases when they need surgery we
support them for surgery
the third scheme that we've been working
on
about three four years now is a program
which we call nehru
which is
again an initiative to provide clean
drinking water to uh municipal schools
uh similarly for you know the focus
being on health the first one was on
road safety the second two are on health
third initiative that we've taken is uh
you know particularly in copenhagen we
realized that
the primary health facility in some of
the rural uh you know this rural town
rural villages in india is very poor so
we've begun to adopt some villages to
provide primary healthcare
uh you know service uh including
equipment and everything else apart from
that during this open period we had a
multiple you know you know csr
initiatives that we that you would have
seen in the video and lastly whenever
there are disasters we step into uh
support you know the community that has
been affected
the other question that you had
in terms of operating model as i said we
even way back in
may of last year
in 2020 just immediately after the
outbreak of combat we announced a policy
to
allow hybrid working where people are
given an option to work from home or
work from office or even partially work
from home partially or from office
right now about 20 percent of our staff
are working from home all the time
balance 80 percent are
either coming to office you know on
every day or some days and that's the
policy that will continue and for which
we've done a lot of work in terms of
training and
empowering people to continue to work
from home through this process and we
believe this is an important uh
initiative both from
employee uh
perspective as also from the
organization perspective in the long
term
uh you had a question on vaccination of
employees as we speak about 84 of our
employees have been vaccinated either in
the camps that we've organized for them
or
through other you know places where we
have compensated therefore they have
vaccination cost
roughly about
you know about seven percent are waiting
vaccination uh that will get done but
some nine percent have some constraints
maybe they have had a covet infection et
cetera so they they will wait for some
time so that will get done very soon so
we are
you know we're not going to get everyone
vaccinated as soon as possible
mr sanaf again thank you for the kind
words you had a question on the female
participation rate i think that's a very
important point that you've made and
this is an important
aspect that all of us look at in fact a
chairperson personally you know drives
that agenda as well
just to give you some numbers over the
last one year the number the percentage
of female employees has moved up from
17.5 to 18.3
it's a small movement but it's in the
right direction as a management we have
a lot of focus on recruiting uh talent
so whenever there are new openings that
open up we uh
particularly focus on improving the
percentage of uh you know female talent
that we are adding
we also believe that this hybrid working
methodology that we have done we are
also
designing or we allow and also scheme
where part-time work will also be
allowed by you know by our employees and
we walk through some of these
initiatives we will be able to attract
more uh female employees uh there are
usually the women friendly policies that
are you know to do with
you know the uh majority benefits
etcetera which are quite progressive in
the context of what happens uh in the
country if you look at our agency force
roughly twenty five percent of our total
agents are uh female agents
uh mr uh rangwala you asked a question
on uh you know government losses
uh if i can look you know share the
numbers for last year last year for the
full financial year we had 49 266
overclaims
uh totaling about
378 crores in terms of reported value of
these games uh the health loss ratio
again largely driven by this overt
impact
you know went worse last year the
previous year 2020 2020 our loss ratio
was 69.9
for health insurance
last year that is fi 2021 the number
went up to 78.00
again largely because of this committing
time
you know your feedback is taken uh you
know i i i i'm asking my secretary
department to reach out to you uh and uh
take you through the process and do the
box that you uh sought
from our perspective we look and looked
at the independent director uh you know
norms they all of them comply with the
company's act provisions but your
feedback is welcome and uh we will
reach out to you to address the concerns
that you have in terms of
you had a few questions in terms of
extra claims
i have answered that in the in the
response to uh mr rangwala
you talked about a question on the capex
on it and that's a very very important
and a very very
you know
critical aspect that we in our
responsibility with the board we spend a
lot of time debating on cyber risk uh we
are doing a level best to uh increase
the strength of our uh perimeter
security the end point security you're
right in the sense that today people are
working from home so you have to work on
uh improving the end point security of
the devices that they work on so there
is a lot of investment that we are
making one of the biggest uh growth in
it spends this last year has been on iot
security so that is clearly an area of
focus for us
and we are as vigilant as one can be in
this aspect
we all understand this is a evolving
field so you know there are actors who
are
uh you know trying to do their best but
we are also as much as possible we are
trying to do our best interval
protecting ourselves uh you had another
question on dividend whether the uh four
will be entering plus four will be in
the final is equal to eight the answer
is yes
four of you was interred and we
announced another four rupees so the
total dividend is eight rupees
uh mr krishna you had a you know quite a
few questions you know one suggestion
that you gave was around thousand and uh
you know we actually have to have
consistency we'll see what we can do and
then the international practice has
become millions and billions that's what
an ic symbol we've been following for
some time but wherever the thousands if
the numbers are large enough we'll see
if we can move them into million so that
it makes easy for you to understand
uh in terms of
the
another question that you had in terms
of dividend
last year
there was a
regulatory uh
had given all insurance companies not to
pay a dividend because of the
uncertainties due to covert that was
lifted towards the end of last year so
we're going to pay one dividend that we
were normally paid which is why the
dividend was was low you had a question
on this june border profits being down
uh the answer is uh
largely through the second covet wave
we had to provide almost 600 additional
claims liability in this quarter uh
simply because of wave 2 has been uh
significantly worse than what we saw
last year in the same quarter last year
same quarter we had roughly 1300 covert
claims this year first quarter we had
close to
almost 50 000 covert claims so it's a
it's a huge increase in poverty claim
that we saw uh this year
uh you also asked a question about fire
holding of 29 being too high honestly
thinking these are my market dynamics
you know we go over and meet all types
of investors but we cannot control who
buys because we are the listed company
uh the holding promoter holding at 51
has been you know reasonably high uh the
gap as you know is 75.75
uh in terms of loss of investment
i don't think there is any major loss of
investment let me just uh
so if you look at the uh we are a
provision for impairment that we have
provided uh last year which was uh 120
this year 66 crores
was reversed
lastly because if you remember end of
the period in 2020 in the month of march
the stock market had collapsed and we
had created a provision which is in line
with a good and a conservative
accounting policy some of that got
released in this water as markets went
back so overall the investment
performance has been quite uh positive
more than 12
absolute return on the investment for
this one
thank you thank you
the queries have now been answered as
mentioned earlier those who have not
cast their vote on the resolution set
forth in the notice may kindly do so now
as the e-voting platform is available
for the next half an hour
i declare the meeting as closed as soon
as the voting on the resolution has been
completed by the members through emoting
i authorize one of the full-time
directors of the company or the company
secretary to declare the results of the
remote e-voting as well as for the
electronic voting done at the agm today
along with the scrutinizers report
the results will be announced within 48
hours from the conclusion of the meeting
that is on or before thursday august 12
2021 to the stock exchanges and shall
also be disseminated on the website of
the company along with the scrutinizers
report
their same would also be duly recorded
as part of the proceedings of the agm
this concludes the formal business of
the meeting
before i conclude on behalf of the
company i wish to place on record our
gratitude to all the shareholders
customers distributors and regulatory
authorities for their cooperation and
active participation in the proceedings
and also for their valuable suggestions
and all their employees for their hard
work and their commitment
thank you all for your support and
cooperation
please take care of yourself
follow all covet protocols and be safe
till we meet again
thank you
you